The sort of argument
for Doomerism to me
is the Fermi paradox
the that we don't
see intelligent life in
our galaxy I was
if you guys have
any on Yeah I've
a lot about that
That can't be the
reason because we should
see all the AIs
that have So just
to clear everyone's the
idea is well it's
sort of unclear why
that would happen right
So if the reason
there's a Fermi paradox
there are no aliens
because they get taken
out by their own
technology we should be
seeing paperclips coming towards
us from some part
of the and apparently
we don't We don't
see any structures Dyson
spheres nothing whether they're
AI or sort of
biological So to me
there has to be
a different answer to
the Fermi paradox I
have my own theories
about that but it's
out of scope for
the next minute But
you I just feel
like
My feeling is that
we're past the great
filter It was probably
multicellular life if I
would have to guess
It was incredibly hard
for biology to evolve
that So we're on
You there isn't a
comfort of what's going
to next I think
it's for us to
write as humanity what's
going to next